Kaspate Wasti, Wakad, Pune.

SHUBHANGI A. KAKADE

+91817-780-9216

shubhangikakade743@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with thorough hands-on experience in all levels of Software Developments, including software development, unit testing, component testing and user acceptance testing. I have experience of working using Agile methodology. I prefer to approach the problem through the meticulous study. Being supportive team player, I prefer to focus on getting things done through collaborative efforts. I am always willing to learn new technologies and take ownership on core things.

| EMPLOYMENT | | |
|-------------------|----------------------------|-------------------------|
| Software Engineer | HCL Technologies Ltd. Pune | December 2018 - Present |

CAMWorks

- Development and implementations of CAD modules in CAMWorks.
- Integration of different CAD tools (SolidWorks, SolidEdge) with CAMWorks
- Working on all aspects of Design and Coding as per requirement of customer.
- Successfully interacting with the Client and taking active part in requirement gathering, providing estimates and technical solutions.

| | Biz Secure Lab Pvt. Ltd. | August 2017 – |
|---------------------------|--------------------------|---------------|
| Trainee Research Engineer | (Net Protector AV) | December 2018 |

NPDataBkp

- The application takes daily, weekly or scheduled data backups and stores it in the drive.
- I developed the algorithm to facilitate the process of storing data .ZIP format using INI file.
- I used MFC and Dynamic Link Libraries (DLLs) to develop the project.

RCALL.EXE

- Manage the internal customer care by routing the calls through internal communication network.
- Worked on the user registration module to get information about users.

| Intern | OpenSpace Solution Pvt. Ltd. | August 2015 – March 2016 |
|--------|------------------------------|--------------------------|
|--------|------------------------------|--------------------------|

Pune Guider for Pune City:

- The web application to help commuters in Pune city find their best routes and most visited places.
- I along with team, had designed architecture and system design of the application.
- I majorly handled the back-end part of the application, developing all the REST APIs requisite for data transfer between front end and back end.

| EDUCATION | | | |
|--------------------|--------------------------------|-----------------------|--|
| | Govt. College of Engineering & | | |
| University of Pune | Research | July 2012 – June 2016 | |

- B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering June 2016. Aggregate Percentage: 74.94.
- Undergraduate Coursework: Operating Systems; Databases; Algorithms; Programming Languages; Comp. Architecture; Engineering Entrepreneurship; Calculus III.

| M. S. B.S.H.S.E (State Board) | Dada Patil Mahavidyalay, | July 2010 – May 2012 |
|-------------------------------|--------------------------|----------------------|
| | Karjat | |

- HSC (Science and Biology) Final Percentage: 77.53
- SSC (Science and Mathematics) Final Percentage: 87.82

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Academic Projects

Pune Guider for Pune City (July 2016): The web application was primarily evolved to help the
citizens with the easy routes across the city from desired source to the destinations. The web
application displays the PMPML schedule for a route along with the emergency numbers for
emergency help and picnic spots located around the city. The application was developed by
leveraging range of technologies like CSS, and HTML for Front End part and JDBC, Mysql for Back End
part.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE AND AWARDS

- University Board Certificate for Sports.
- · Selection in University Zonal Team of Kho-Kho
- Player of the Year 2014-15
- · Marathon Winner's Award for three consecutive years
- Event management in technical event organized by GCOEARA

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- C++, VC++, MFC, Visual Studio 2010, Visual Studio 2015, Visual Studio 2017
- MySQL, SQL, MFC Database
- Software Development and Testing; Agile/Scrum methodology; Open Source Contribution
- Windows XP; Vista; Windows 2007; Windows Server 2012; Ubuntu; Android 5.1.
- Google Vision API, HTML, CSS, C, Python, Computer Networking.